Sometimes, we wake with anxiety...
and edgy energy.
What will happen today?
What is in store for me?
So many questions.
We want resolution,
solid earth under our feet,
so we take life into our own hands.
We take action, yeah?
Our solutions
are temporary.
They are quick fix.
They create more anxiety,
more suffering.
There is no resolution to life's questions.
It is easier to be patient
once we finally accept
there is no resolution.
Shit! I'm running
out of nerves! Shit! Chest
cavity. Frank.
Have you ever ha- heard of the black mamba?
Frank! Hey, man!
What are you doing?
You want to hang out?
I'm just showing off my moves.
What are you doing?
I got to go.
We didn't even get into the ice yet. I
got to catch a plane.
Wait a second.
Wait a second. Hey.
Ah, come on. Hey, man.
You're not gonna chase me ov- over here.
Come on.
Wait, let's... Oh, yeah.
Come on, man. What's happening?
Where you going?
You know what's happening?
You know, I, I gotta go.
I gotta go, man. Ah!
I told you, I have to go.
You gotta go? Yeah.
Well, y- well,
the ladies are here, man.
What's the matter? Stay, okay?
I need you to...
Don't you like me anymore?
I just have to go. I have to go.
You're my guy.
Look- Hey, you started it.
You finish- I can't finish it without you.
You finish it.
That's not part of the deal.
Hey, there they are.
Look at this. Look at this.
Ladies, come on.
He's, he's saying no. Rick! Rick!
Rick! Rick! Rick!
Hi.
Oh, morning.
How'd you sleep?
I slept okay.
Have you seen Lori?
Not yet.
Should we see if she wants to get some
breakfast?
Yeah, I'll go ask her. No,
I'll do it.
Kate and I are going to go get breakfast.
You want to come?
Oh,
I think I'm going to keep sleeping, if
that's okay.
Listen, I'm sorry about Valentin.
Honestly, had no idea you didn't care.
Jack, please, I...
I want to be your friend.
We can talk about it later when you're not
sleeping.
You want us to bring you back something?
No, thanks.
Okay.
I think I should wait till we're home,
you know, before I tell mom. Like,
could you wait till she's back on her meds?
Tell mom what?
That I'm coming with you.
What?
Lachlan, I don't want to be responsible
for fucking up your life, okay?
Just let me fuck up my own life,
all right?
They're back.
Oh, hi.
How was it?
How did it go?
Um,
it was, uh...
You know what,
can we actually talk about it later? I
just, I want to shower and- Huh,
we'll talk about it at breakfast. Okay.
Lachlan?
What?
Tell us.
I don't fucking know anything, okay?
Belinda.
Hey.
Um, this is my son, Zion.
Yeah, yeah, we met mom.
Right, on the boat.
Yeah. Right.
Um,
do you want to join us?
It's okay.
I just saw you and just wanted to say
hello.
Hello.
Um,
bye. Bye.
Sugar? Wow, you,
you like this guy. I don't know.
Well, he likes you.
You know,
he wants to go into business together.
Really? Mm-hmm.
The spa you always talked about? Hmm.
Where would we even do it, Ray?
Wherever you want.
Hawaii? Here?
He ain't got no money and neither do I.
I don't even know where I would get it.
I don't know investors like that.
Hello?
Do I have to say it?
Z? What? I already told you.
I'm not taking that blood money,
okay? Mom.
Listen, $100,000 isn't enough anyway.
We would need more than that,
so drop it.
What if it were a million dollars?
But it's not. Okay.
No, you told him you would get back to him.
Why don't you just see how much you can
get?
Z- You don't have to go through with it,
just see.
See how much you can get.
I mean, you're always gonna wonder. If
I go up there and negotiate with him,
then I don't do it,
it'll piss him off and then he'll fuck me
up.
No, no. He won't do anything to you.
He's done it before.
'Cause I'll be there.
And then, plus,
you'll need a professional to help you
negotiate this deal anyways, so...
So, you liked it at the center?
Yeah, it's a really cool place.
Great.
Yeah. It's not a cult.
Well, I think it's great that,
that you've
proved to yourself that you can
live a simple life like that. It'll all
be fine without less, right?
Yeah.
What?
Like, the f- the food.
I mean, it was, it was vegetarian,
but it...
I don't know, you could tell it,
like, wasn't organic.
And
it was just kinda bland and...
I don't know, it was kinda like,
"Could I, like,
really eat this for a whole year?"
And then... Oh, God.
And then I went back to my room and it was
this, like,
tiny little box with, like,
a mattress with stains on it and no air
conditioning and...
I, I, I know, I know,
I know I'm not supposed to be attached to
this kind of stuff and I don't wanna think
that I am, but like...
I don't know. I think I am.
Oh.
I know I am.
Like, the idea that I'm, like ,
that I'm, like,
this princess who needs things to be a
certain way, it's
just so pathetic.
It's not pathetic.
No, mom, it is,
it is pathetic and, like
, I don't know, like,
I guess I am spoiled 'cause,
like, 'cause like,
I can't live like that.
Oh, sweetie.
You don't have to prove anything.
There's so much suffering in the world and
we have it so easy, and,
like, other people have it so hard and I
just...
I feel like it's really unfair.
And I just feel really bad.
We're lucky. It's true.
Huh. No one in the history of the world
has lived better than we have.
Even the old kings and queens.
The least we can do is enjoy it.
If we don't, it's offensive.
It's an offense to all the billions of
people
who can only dream
that one day they could live like we do.
Yeah. Oh, baby. Come here.
I'm really sorry I brought you guys here.
Oh,
baby. Oh. I love you so much.
Hey. Hey.
If you, uh,
if you made one of your shakes,
I'd drink it.
No, I already had one earlier.
Stuff's on the counter if you wanna make
one, though.
No one's gonna make you a man.
Okay? You gotta do it yourself.
All right, I'll see you later.
Well, where are you going?
Just
down to the beach.
You want me to come?
I'm just gonna go read for a little bit.
All right, see you.
Are you mad or something?
Okay. Dude, it...
Look, like, it,
it's okay for you to, like,
worship me, but don't, like...
Worship me.
You know what I mean?
Look,
all you care about is getting off and
I saw you lying there and I thought
you looked a little left out.
And I'm, you know,
a pleaser.
I just wanna give everyone what they want,
and I'm in a family full of narcissists.
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
Let's just drop this, like,
forever. Please.
Okay?
Sí, yo también.
Hwaddee krupp, P' Lek. Ai'tok nekrab.
Ngo rwo wa ni wan hwut, pee.
Tew pee wang 'ea.
Choy telefon glub khong pom dewy.
Pom reung laen raut ce kub.
How are you, my friend?
Did you like the fights?
I'll look for you after.
I was on a date,
and you were busy with
two men.
Are they your friends?
Maybe some guys I know from the gym.
What are their names?
Why do you wanna know their names?
I think I've seen them before.
I don't know.
Some good fights, though, huh?
I'll see you soon.
Hey.
You brought my book.
Yep.
Read it. It'll change your life.
I'm almost finished.
You've read the whole thing already?
I went to Duke.
Okay, genius. What'd you think?
Yeah, I mean,
I thought that the sex
stuff was pretty interesting. Mm-hmm.
Should read the other ones I gave you as
well.
She's amazing.
They're not about sex,
but the laws of the universe,
how we're all connected.
Hmm. She has this theory that there are
different groups, and
we're in these groups with people we know
and people we don't know.
And these groups are working together to
fulfill this divine plan.
And sometimes you don't even know you're
in the same group as someone else, so
you and I,
we could be in the same group and not even
know it.
Hey. Hi. Oh. Ah.
How did it go?
Well, I didn't kill anyone.
Well, that's good. Yeah.
Yeah. I said what I had to say.
Mm-hmm. Got the monkey off my back.
I missed you.
Yeah.
Hey.
Sorry I couldn't help you out last night.
It's fine.
We'll find someone else.
Won't be hard.
Well, if it makes you happy, get on.
You know what you should get?
Highlights. Just right here.
Hey, Dad. Oh, hi.
Hey, Walky.
Yeah?
Think you could live
with no money?
I mean, no money. No house, nothing.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I could.
Think you could?
Hey, uh, it's your last day.
Don't just sit in here.
Go, go do something. All right?
Go swim or...
Go
on. All right.
Later, Dad. Yeah.
I know you know.
Please don't say anything.
If you do, I'm dead.
They will deport me,
I go back to my country. I'm dead.
My friends, all of us are dead.
They can't work.
They have no way to make money here.
If you say something,
you're killing me.
You're killing me. Melody?
Um, I'm not sure if you've heard,
but the Hollingers are
coming back tomorrow morning.
They are hoping to say hello to Ms.
Lemon and take a photo with her before she
leaves.
I'll let them know.
Can you find out if she's okay with a
photo?
We might post it on the hotel's website.
It's very important to Kunzita Laa.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, sawasdee kah.
Good morning. Um,
I was just gonna put these on the table.
They're your phones and things. In
fact, uh, he's back- No.
Don't, don't do that.
So, I'll just- Please. No? Yeah.
W- we don't w- want 'em.
We don't, we don't need 'em. Okay.
Are you enjoying having a break from your
phone?
Yeah. Do you know what I could do? I
could put these on the hotel boat that
takes you to the airport tomorrow,
and that way you can detox till the very
last minute.
Yeah. Sure. Let's do that. Okay.
Yeah. Pam, uh, when we got here,
you said something about this fruit.
Remind me what you said about it?
Oh, yes.
Uh, the seeds of the fruit are poison.
Oh, right. Yeah. Yeah.
The locals actually call it the suicide
tree, because
people grind up the seeds and eat them
when they want to kill themselves.
So, don't eat it.
I don't think you'd want to anyway. It
doesn't taste very nice.
Have a wonderful last day. Thanks.
Sawasdee kah.
Can I get you any drinks?
No, we're okay. Uh, two whiskeys.
Rocks, please. Certainly, sir.
Yeah, thank you.
Trust me.
We're gonna need it.
Mom,
you know how you always say
you always gotta be prepared because you
never know when you're gonna get your
moment?
This could be it, mom.
Don't miss your moment.
He killed the bitch. I know.
Look, maybe this is the one good thing
that's meant to come out of all of it.
I mean, think about it.
This place is killer, man. You're, uh,
you are balling.
Thank you.
I thought we'd be talking privately.
Sorry. Zion.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm her only son.
We're a team.
It's just how it's always been.
But don't trip.
You know, cone of silence.
Uh, business major, U of H.
I don't care about what you did,
what you're gonna do.
All I care about is business and the
bottom line.
MBA, baby.
Hey.My mom brought me up to speed,
uh, on your initial offer.
Unfortunately, it's gonna be a pass.
Oh, is that right?
She's just caught up in the ethics of it
all.
She just doesn't think the guilt and the
emotional stress would be worth it, so...
And she wants to focus on starting her own
business 'cause that's her dream.
That was the point of the money.
Yeah, but
that amount of money isn't gonna get it
done, you
know? I mean,
for her to take on this kind of risk with
you,
you know,
she would need to feel like her dream is
coming true, like
full on.
I mean, you got your dream here.
She's gotta get hers, right?
I mean,
what happens to a dream deferred?
You know,
does it dry up like a raisin in the sun?
Hers has been deferred a long time.
Might explode.
Uh, point is,
is there enough money here for everyone to
get their happy ending?
I think so.
So, how much would it take for her to get
her happy ending?
Well, we crunched the numbers,
Greg, and if we're being realistic,
all in, soup to nuts,
five million
.
That's not happening.
Look, I know that's a big ask,
but I did do a little research,
and according to the internet, uh,
your wife, late wife, ex-wife,
uh, former wife, rest in peace,
was worth at least half a billion dollars.
Don't believe everything you read.
Oh, I know.
I- I found some very public records where
that number pretty much checks out.
So, what we're asking for is a mere one
percent of your total haul.
We get that,
and we are ride or die 'til the day we die.
We are Team Gary.
I mean,
peace of mind is worth one percent,
don't you think?
I mean, and you won't miss it.
I mean, what?
You're gonna- you're gonna spend through
all five hundred mil here?
Come on man,
how many years you got left anyway, right?
I'm not doing this.
He's not giving us any money,
and this is a waste of time. Okay?
Now let's go.
Zion! Okay mom,
why don't you just give us
businessmen a minute alone? No.
I mean it.
Hey, hey,
hey. What are you doing?
I was just making my big pitch.
You go back in there and you tell him your
mother takes things very personal.
She doesn't trust him, okay?
And if we don't make a deal and we don't
get the money,
who knows what I'll do?
Look at you playing hard ball.
Yes, mom. Shh.
Just tell him that your mother's a very
honest lady, okay?
But he better come through.
He wants us to be scared,
but we gotta make him scared, okay?
Now go close it.
Yeah.
ว่าไง นี่รีบตอกบัตรแล้วรีบออกมาหาไรเนี่ย
เป็นไรเปล่า พี่ว่าพี่ควรจะลาออกจากงานเนี
้ย
พี่ไม่เหมาะจะเป็นยามอะ ทำไมพี่พูดงั้นอะ
พี่มาคิดดูว่า
ถ้าเป็นพระพุทธเจ้า
ท่านจะทำยังไง
พี่ไม่อยากทำร้ายใครอะ นี่...
พี่ตั้งใจทำงานที่นี่มาตั้งหลายปี อยู่ดี ๆ
จะทิ้งมันแล้วก็ไปเริ่มต้นจากศูนย์ ที่ไหนก็
ไม่รู้เหรอมุกว่าพี่ใจเย็นก่อนนะ
อย่าคิดมากเลย พระพุทธเจ้าเลยเหรอ
พี่ว่าพี่หางานอื่นได้อยู่แล้ว พี่เป
็นคนหนักเอาเบาสู้
มุกเห็นความมั่นใจของพี่นะ แล้วมุกก็เชื่อว่
าสักวันนึงพี่จะต้องประสบความสำเร็จ
พี่ว่าพี่จะรู้สึกดีแล้วก็มีความมั่นใจถ้าเก
ิดพี่ได้ทำในสิ่งที่พี่คิดว่าถูกอะ
แล้วคืนนี้อยากไปกินข้าวที่ไหนอะ
ไว้ก่อนแล้วกันนะ พอดีแม่เจ็บหลังแล้วต้องรี
บกลับไปช่วยทำงานบ้าน โอเค แล้วพรุ่งนี้อะ
เฮ้อ ขอคิดดูก่อนนะ
เดี๋ยวไปละ
ไว้เจอกัน
Boys,
it's time to go to dinner. Let's go.
Hey, uh, miss. Excuse me. Uh,
w- it's your last night and I thought that
it might be, uh,
fun if we made cocktails in the room later.
Pina coladas.
Uh, could you bring some rum and mixtures to
the villa? Get
them sent there?
We have a blender.
Yes, I'll let them know. Great.
Pina coladas? Yeah.
It's your last night, so...
I've never had a pina colada.
Are they good?
You're not gonna have one tonight either.
You're not 21.
Sucks.
Hi. Oh. Hi. You made it.
Yeah. So pretty. Aw.
I thought you were gonna miss our last
dinner.
I just had a late night.
How was it? Was it fun? What'd you do?
Uh,
I went to the fight thing,
which was whatever.
And then I went back with Alexi to his
apartment.
Uh, okay. Alexi.
Ladies.
How was your last day? So nice.
Yeah. Relaxing. Yeah.
I wanted to remind you about your morning
massages and tell you, um,
the owners are arriving tomorrow,
Miss Satila and her husband,
and they were hoping to take a photo with
you.
Would that be all right?
Yeah, of course.
Yes, ladies, um, enjoy your dinner.
Too nervous to eat.
He was supposed to close it.
He said he was gonna think about it.
But I gave him your account number and the
routing number and,
like, he could wire the money tonight.
There's a line between positive thinking
and delusional.
You're crossing the line, babe.
Go big or go home, right?
In a goddamn body bag.
Okay, that's enough.
Hey, what are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm checking my account is what I'm
doing over here getting my hopes up.
All right. You're
free.
It's a new day.
Told you you had nothing to worry about.
Of course I was worried. I love you.
But, you know, I was never too worried
because amor fati.
Do you know what that means?
I don't know what that means.
It means you have to embrace your fate,
good or bad. Whatever will be will be.
You know?
And at this point we're linked,
so if a bad thing happens to you, it
happens to me.
Mm.
I think we're gonna be together forever,
don't
you?
That's the plan.
Is it?
Yeah.
I'm so glad we did this.
Me too.
Thank you for organizing
Jack and Peg for the villa.
Are you sure we can't help pay?
No, no, it was my total pleasure.
Um, well, our pastor at our church
talks about how
there's a time in life
after years of, you know,
watering and weeding and nurturing your
soil,
and then one day, you look around
and your garden is in bloom.
And that's how I feel right now.
Everything is in bloom.
All our flowers are in bloom.
I've just been in the mood all week. I
really have. I mean, I can
do yoga and meditate and whatever, but
nothing,
you know,
for me makes me feel more grounded than,
you know, being with friends,
real friends.
It's a lonely world.
It can be, you know?
People judge you for your superficial
defects, and
you guys judged me for my profound defects.
No. You know what I mean. Yeah.
And, uh,
I've just been on cloud nine all week,
and I really needed it, so thank you.
That's funny 'cause if I'm being honest,
all week, I've just been so sad.
What?
I just f- feel like my expectations were
too high, or...
I just feel like
as you get older,
you have to justify your life,
you know,
and your choices. And
when I'm with you guys,
it's just so, like,
like, transparent what my choices were,
and my mistakes.
I have no belief system, and I...
Well, I mean,
I've had a lot of them, but...
I mean,
work was my religion for forever,
but I definitely lost my belief there.
And then, and then I tried love,
and, and that was just a painful religion.
It just made everything worse.
And then, even for me, just,
like, being a mother,
that didn't save me either.
But I had this epiphany today.
I don't need religion or God to give my
life meaning
because time gives it meaning.
We, we started this life together.
I mean, we're,
we're going through it apart,
but we're still together, and I,
I look at you guys,
and it feels meaningful.
And, and I can't explain it,
but even when we're just sitting around
the pool talking about whatever and named
shit, it still feels very fucking deep.
I'm glad you have a beautiful face,
and I'm glad that you have a beautiful
life.
And I'm just happy to be at the table.
I love you. I
love you.
I love you. I love yous.
I can't even accept, like,
one glass? You-
you need to get a Coke.
Come on.
Okay.
Lachy, can- Yeah, I'm coming.
Um,
I couldn't ask for a more perfect family.
We've had a perfect life. Haven't we?
No privations, no
suffering. Yeah. No trauma.
A- and my job is to keep all that
from you. To, to keep you safe.
Because I love you.
I love you so much.
We love you too. You do.
We love you, dad. We love you, dad.
I'd like to make a toast to Thailand.
And
I just can't wait to get back home.
But to Thailand, thank you.
Khob khun krab. Khob khun ka.
Khob khun, kob, khob kun ka.
Okay. Pina colada? Hmm?
Smells weird. No. No.
No.
It's strong, but it's fine.
It's fine. Drink it. Drink it.
You're good. Drink it.
. Oh.
Oh, god. Dude. Dude.
It's, uh, the, you know,
the- What? Coconut milk is off.
Tim. It's the coco- coconut milk is off.
Put it back.
The coconut milk is off.
Okay, the coconut milk is off.
No, no, no. No, no. Don't drink it.
All good.
Uh.
Okay.
I'll, I'll see you.
I'll see you in the morning.
Is that it, Tim?
Have you ever heard of wine?
What? There are several bottles of wine in
the cabinet right behind you.
Yeah. You know? Yeah.
Lachlan, why don't you get an opener and
get some glasses, uh-
Get some towels. ...
a few glasses of wine?
Ew. Do you want to start- Piper,
can you get the glasses? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Holy
shit, ma. I called the bank.
It's real. Are you kidding?
And then Greg called.
And w- w- what,
what did he say?
He said he gave it to Tanya
as much as he gave it to me. It's-
it's what she would've wanted.
And he said
he wanted to make sure I lived up to my
end of the bargain.
And, and, and wha- what'd you say?
I said that I would. Yes, mom!
Yes! Yes! Wait, wait, wait.
I'm nervous,
but I just gotta wrap up some things
today and then we're gonna be outta here.
Wha-
wha- get outta where? Thailand.
I don't wanna be down the road
from him when he changes his mind.
No, the money's already in the bank,
bro. But still,
I'm gonna be hard to find.
You know what I'm saying? Okay.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um, um,
what about your man?
You two were gonna start a business
together.
Don't you wanna start your own spa?
Can't I just be rich for five fucking
minutes?
Yes. Yes, you can. I can? Yes, you can.
Yes, we can.
Yeah.
Okay, look. Listen.
Um, why don't you go get ready,
okay? I booked a treatment for you.
It's stress management and you're gonna
need it.
What? No, no, no, no.
I don't need that, ma.
We're too blessed to be stressed.
Look, it's too late to cancel and if I'm
paying, you're
going, so- Okay. Go get ready.
Mom.
She's a Cancer-Venus so it's very intense,
and he's an Aquarius-Moon.
It's like, babe,
it's never gonna happen. Right.
He's never gonna give you what you need.
He's gonna withhold forever. Hey.
Can we pick up that story in just a second?
I'm still really hungry.
Oh, can you get me a donut?
You got it. Donut.
Well, look who it is.
You come into my house,
lie to my wife.
Get the fuck outta here.
We're on the first boat.
I don't want anything to do with you.
I remember your mother.
Yeah.
I knew she was a drunk and a slut,
didn't know she was a liar too.
Wanted you to think your father was some
kinda great man.
She told you a fairytale, kid.
Your father
was no saint.
You didn't miss out on much,
and that's the fucking truth.
What?
You're gonna try to kill me now?
I don't think so.
What is it? He's here.
Who? Just insulted my fucking mother.
Forget about him,
okay?
You're free, remember?
You're over it. How could...
How can I get over everything he's taken
from me?
He took my whole
fucking life.
Just stop worrying about the love he didn'
t get.
Think about the love you have.
I love you.
I'm right here.
Are you going to get the
goddamn breakfast up there?
Are you all blind or what?
Please don't do something stupid.
Uh,
I'm- I'm fine. I gotta- I gotta go.
You're really freaking me out.
I'm just gonna go see my lady.
What lady? The Indian lady.
That's it. What did I do?
Go on then. I'm going to be okay.
Shit.
Hey.
Yo.
What book are you reading?
What book?
The one in your hand.
Oh. I don't know.
Here, it's like a... Morning.
It's a book. Whatever.
I'm going to let your father sleep. He
needs it.
Okay, let's go.
Lachlan, sweetheart, breakfast.
Lachie, come on.
Okay, just meet us up there.
The treatment center, uh, uh,
room is over there by the big blue bed.
Mom,
breathe.
Okay? We did that shit. Yeah.
We did that shit. Yeah, we did.
And you worked so hard, mom.
Good things happen to good people.
You're right.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Now go on.
Find your center or some shit.
Zion?
Yes, ma'am.
I will be sitting with you this morning.
Right this way.
How are you?
I'm very well, thank you.
How are you doing?
Hey. Hey.
Hi.
I'll be right with you. I-
I- I really...
I- I- I need to talk to you.
I have a session. This is urgent.
Okay, please?
I just need a few minutes of your time.
I can meet you after.
No. No. Uh,
just sit on this bench.
I'll have them bring you a clean blanket.
I need to talk to you now.
Please?
Look,
you'll be all right. Okay?
I'll come find you.
I promise.
Just give me one hour. One hour.
Sorry. I'll come find you.
Locke?
Locke!
Sir!
Wake up. Hey.
Wake up!
Sir!
Come on. Come on. Co- come on. Come on
now.
Help!
Help! Help! Somebody help!
How were the massages?
Oh, fantastic.
We had to sneak one last in before we
leave.
Thank you for agreeing to a photo.
Oh. Hi.
May I introduce you to my husband, Hsu.
We love your show. Aw.
Well, we love your hotel. Good.
Oh, Belinda.
How are you today?
Good, yeah. Um,
how are you? I'm good, as usual.
Pornchai, um,
I've really loved getting to know you,
but,
some things have changed for me, and
I'm gonna be leaving Thailand tomorrow.
Uh, le- leaving
tomorrow?
What about, um,
starting a business?
You, me? Maybe.
But,
circumstances have changed for me,
and I just can't commit to anything right
now.
I'm so sorry.
Uh,
would you mind very much if we took a
picture together? Oh,
of course. Okay. Okay. Okay?
I'll go over here. Okay. Yes.
Come, come, come.
Beautiful.
Wow. That's beautiful.
One more. One more. Yeah, yeah.
Okay. And maybe one of you will sit there.
Oh, yes. Yes. Okay.
Wow. It's beautiful.
Could Jim get the camera? Yeah.
Thank you so much.
Ah!
Surprise! Oh, yeah. That's good.
That's good for Jim. Yeah.
Yeah. The wife we have.
Rick?
Get out of here.
Out of here.
Smile.
Oh, my God.
Fuck you.
Oh, God!
Jim. Are you okay?
Are you okay? Go, go, go.
Go. Jim. Jim. Why?
He killed my father.
He's your father.
He's your father. He told me.
Go, go, go, go.
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, no.
You're okay. All right?
You're going to be okay.
You hear me? You hear me?
You can't die on me, okay?
Chelsea.
No.
No. No!
Hey.
Hey! Help me, please.
I'm
sorry. I'm so sorry.
We're going to be together forever, okay?
Just like you said.
I think I just saw God.
Oh, God.
Kids, look what I have.
Hey,
guys. Wait.
Things are about to change.
We'll get through it
as a family.
Because we're-
we're a strong family and- and,
you know,
nothing's more important than family,
right?
Woo!
Nothing from nothing leaves nothing.
You gotta have something if you wanna be
with me.
Nothing from nothing leaves nothing.
You gotta have something if you wanna be
with me.
I'm not trying to be your hero
because that's zero,
it's too cold for me.
I'm not trying to be your highest 'cause
that, minus,
is too low to see. Yeah.
Well, no.
Hey.
Nothing from nothing leaves nothing.
And I'm not stuffing, believe you me.
Don't you remember I told ya?
I'm a soldier in the war on poverty.
Yeah. Yes, I am.